AZEEM ALI

W E B D E V E L O P E R



✓ imazeemali97@gmail.com

Bage-e-Malir, Karachi

linked.com/azeemali97

PROFILE

I am a frontend and WordPress developer with nearly 6 years of experience in WordPress and 2 years in frontend development. I have designed and developed a wide range of websites across various industries worldwide. Additionally, I work with different CMS platforms, including Shopify and Webflow, and have a strong background in web design and UI/UX.

SKILLS

- Web Design
- Design Thinking
- Wireframe Creation
- Front End Coding
- Problem-Solving
- Debugging and troubleshooting.
- Project Management Tools
- Strong Communication

EXPERIENCE

FRONTEND & WORDPRESS DEVELOPER

Devcode Digital

2022 - Present

- Create detailed and visually appealing website designs using Figma.
- Build websites from scratch using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
- Develop WordPress websites using various plugins, including:
 Woocommerce, Bricks, Elementor, and Divi etc.

WORDPRESS DEVELOPER

Design Henge

2021 - 2022

- Develop WordPress websites using various plugins, including:
 Woocommerce, Bricks, Elementor, and Divi etc.
- Design and develop websites using Webflow.

WORDPRESS & SHOPFIY DEVELOPER

Adlevate Digital Marketing

2021 - 2021

- Develop WordPress websites using various plugins, including: Woocommerce, Bricks, Elementor, and Divi etc.
- Develop and set up e-commerce stores on Shopify.

EDUCATION

MATRIC

Shaheen Secondary School 2010 - 2014

HIGHER DIPLOMA IN SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

Aptech Metro Star Gate

2016 - 2019

LANGUAGES

- URDU
- ENGLISH

C O D I N G L A N G U A G E

- HTML/CSS
- JAVASCRIPT
- PHP
- SQL

FRAMEWORK &LIBRARY

- BOOTSTRAP
- TAILWIND CSS
- GSAP
- SWIPER JS
- JQUERY

SOFTWARE & TOOLS

- VSCODE
- FIGMA
- CANVA
- GITHUB DESKTOP
- CHATGPT
- TRELLO
- DEBUGGER
- CPANEL

WORDPRESS DEVELOPER

STL Design Lab

2021 - 2021

Develop WordPress websites using various plugins, including:
 Woocommerce, Bricks, Elementor, and Divi etc.

WORDPRESS & SHOPFIY DEVELOPER

PCKEY CALLOUT LIMITED

2020 - 2021

- Develop WordPress websites using various plugins, including:
 Woocommerce, Bricks, Elementor, and Divi etc.
- Upload Product on Prestashop Website.

WORK PORTFOLIO

tothecorelagree.com samshairandbeauty.co.uk

digimove.ae bellegateaucafe.com

CMS & NO CODE TOOLS

- WordPress
- WebFlow
- FlutterFlow

- Shopify
- Bubble.io